[{"body": [{"stem": "连一连，找出相同积木搭起来的图形。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合5.svg", "val": "0"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合6.svg", "val": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合4.svg", "val": "2"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合2.svg", "val": "0"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合1.svg", "val": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合3.svg", "val": "2"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect3"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 0], [2, 2]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-7-04"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，找出相同积木搭起来的图形。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合5.svg", "val": "0"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合6.svg", "val": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合4.svg", "val": "2"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合2.svg", "val": "0"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合1.svg", "val": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合3.svg", "val": "2"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect3"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 0], [2, 2]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-7-04"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，找出相同积木搭起来的图形。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合5.svg", "val": "0"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合6.svg", "val": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合4.svg", "val": "2"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合2.svg", "val": "0"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合1.svg", "val": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合3.svg", "val": "2"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect3"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 0], [2, 2]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-7-04"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，找出相同积木搭起来的图形。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合5.svg", "val": "0"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合6.svg", "val": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合4.svg", "val": "2"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合1.svg", "val": "0"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合3.svg", "val": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合2.svg", "val": "2"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect3"}], "answers": [[0, 0], [1, 2], [2, 1]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-7-04"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，找出相同积木搭起来的图形。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合5.svg", "val": "0"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合6.svg", "val": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合4.svg", "val": "2"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合3.svg", "val": "0"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合1.svg", "val": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合2.svg", "val": "2"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect3"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 2], [2, 0]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-7-04"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，找出相同积木搭起来的图形。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合5.svg", "val": "0"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合6.svg", "val": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合4.svg", "val": "2"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合3.svg", "val": "0"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合2.svg", "val": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合1.svg", "val": "2"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect3"}], "answers": [[0, 2], [1, 1], [2, 0]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-7-04"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，找出相同积木搭起来的图形。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合5.svg", "val": "0"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合6.svg", "val": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合4.svg", "val": "2"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合3.svg", "val": "0"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合1.svg", "val": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合2.svg", "val": "2"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect3"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 2], [2, 0]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-7-04"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，找出相同积木搭起来的图形。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合5.svg", "val": "0"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合6.svg", "val": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合4.svg", "val": "2"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合1.svg", "val": "0"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合2.svg", "val": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合3.svg", "val": "2"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect3"}], "answers": [[0, 0], [1, 1], [2, 2]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-7-04"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，找出相同积木搭起来的图形。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合5.svg", "val": "0"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合6.svg", "val": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合4.svg", "val": "2"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合1.svg", "val": "0"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合3.svg", "val": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合2.svg", "val": "2"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect3"}], "answers": [[0, 0], [1, 2], [2, 1]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-7-04"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，找出相同积木搭起来的图形。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合5.svg", "val": "0"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合6.svg", "val": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合4.svg", "val": "2"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合2.svg", "val": "0"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合3.svg", "val": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合1.svg", "val": "2"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect3"}], "answers": [[0, 2], [1, 0], [2, 1]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-7-04"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，找出相同积木搭起来的图形。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合5.svg", "val": "0"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合6.svg", "val": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合4.svg", "val": "2"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合3.svg", "val": "0"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合1.svg", "val": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合2.svg", "val": "2"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect3"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 2], [2, 0]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-7-04"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，找出相同积木搭起来的图形。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合5.svg", "val": "0"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合6.svg", "val": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合4.svg", "val": "2"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合2.svg", "val": "0"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合1.svg", "val": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合3.svg", "val": "2"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect3"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 0], [2, 2]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-7-04"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，找出相同积木搭起来的图形。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合5.svg", "val": "0"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合6.svg", "val": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合4.svg", "val": "2"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合1.svg", "val": "0"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合2.svg", "val": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合3.svg", "val": "2"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect3"}], "answers": [[0, 0], [1, 1], [2, 2]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-7-04"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，找出相同积木搭起来的图形。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合5.svg", "val": "0"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合6.svg", "val": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合4.svg", "val": "2"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合2.svg", "val": "0"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合3.svg", "val": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合1.svg", "val": "2"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect3"}], "answers": [[0, 2], [1, 0], [2, 1]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-7-04"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，找出相同积木搭起来的图形。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合5.svg", "val": "0"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合6.svg", "val": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合4.svg", "val": "2"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合3.svg", "val": "0"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合1.svg", "val": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合2.svg", "val": "2"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect3"}], "answers": [[0, 1], [1, 2], [2, 0]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-7-04"}, {"body": [{"stem": "连一连，找出相同积木搭起来的图形。", "content": [[{"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合5.svg", "val": "0"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合6.svg", "val": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合4.svg", "val": "2"}], [{"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合2.svg", "val": "0"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合3.svg", "val": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/立体图形组合/立体图形组合_连线/组合1.svg", "val": "2"}]], "type": "know-cube-connect3"}], "answers": [[0, 2], [1, 0], [2, 1]], "knowledges": ["立体图形的拼组"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-7-04"}]